https://www.posterpop.com/privacy-policy/

Other Merch
Warehouse Finds!
Clearance Sale!
Artists
Marco AlmeraVince RayBigToeSHAGDirty DonnyKozikCoopPizzGustavo RimadaPigors
View All Artists
Additional Information
Home
Artists
Aaron MarshallBigToeCandyCoopDerek YanigerDirty DonnyForbesKozikKruseMarco AlmeraPigorsPizzSHAGTara McPhersonVince RayVon FrancoBen Von StrawnOther Artists
Genre
Hula TikiSkulls - Day of the DeadHotrod Motorcycle ScooterCats Dogs Wolves AnimalsTattooRockabilly Music Rock and RollDevil and DevilgirlRetro 50s-60s Modern Futuristic 70sMonsters FinksPinup SexyReligiousSurf Skate SportDrinking Drunk
Men's Shirts
Aaron Marshall T-ShirtsAlmera T-ShirtsBigToe T-ShirtsBen Von Strawn T-ShirtsDerek Yaniger T-ShirtsGustavo T-ShirtsDirty Donny T-ShirtsForbes T-ShirtsKozik T-ShirtsKruse T-ShirtsMcPherson T-ShirtsPigors T-ShirtsPizz T-ShirtsVon Franco T-ShirtsVince Ray T-ShirtsClearance T-ShirtsNewest T-Shirts
Blog
Women's
Aaron Marshall BabydollsAlmera BabydollsBen Von Strawn Baby DollsBig Toe BabydollsDerek Yaniger Baby DollsDirty Donny BabydollsForbes BabydollsGustavo BabydollsKozik BabydollsKruse BabydollsPigors BabydollsPizz BabydollsTara McPherson BabydollsVince Ray BabydollsWomen's Baby Doll Tees and Tank TopsNewest Women's ApparelWoman's Sale and Clearance
Stickers
Almera StickersAlmera ReligiousAaron Marshall StickersBigToe StickersCoop StickersDerek Yaniger StickersDirty Donny StickersForbes StickersKozik StickersKruse StickersPigors StickersPizz StickersShag StickersTara McPherson StickersTyson McAdoo StickersVon Franco StickersVince Ray Sticker
Patches
Almera PatchesDirty Donny PatchesCoop PatchesForbes PatchesKozik PatchesKruse PatchesPigors PatchesPizz PatchesScrojo PatchesTara McPherson PatchesVon Franco PatchesVince Ray PatchesDan Collins, Reed, Von Spoon PatchesFD PatchesPLP Patches
Fridge Magnets
Other Merchandise
Tattoo FlashArtists BooksHats and BeaniesMisc MerchClearance
Art and Editions
Fine Art FAQOriginal ArtLimited Edition PrintsArtist's Silkscreen PostersArtist Hand Signed Prints
Custom Printing
Custom Giclee Printing and Art Capture PhotographyCustom Sticker Printing
RSS Syndication
Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
Call us on
My Account
Gift Certificates
Wish Lists
Sign in or Create an account
Search
Categories
Artists
Other Merch
Warehouse Finds!
Clearance Sale!
Hats and Beanies
Artists Books
Tattoo Flash Sets
Info
Poster Pop Collection Art Show
Contact
Custom Art Reproduction
Custom Sticker Printing
Last Updated: May 24, 2018
Poster Pop respects your privacy. We only send emails out to our private list maybe 5-10 times a year, only to notify our list about Poster Pop Specific activities! We will only send out emails directly about your order status and about shipping. We periodically send out emails using our BigCommerce Website and MailChimp notifying our list about Sales, New Artists, New Merchandise, Poster Pop Events, and Poster Pop activities. Nothing Else!! We do not Share, nor do we Sell your information in any way!! You can opt out anytime!!
Personal Information Collected
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Personal Information you have given us.
We collect Personal Information from you through online forms, emails we send that you read and click, the pages you visit on our website after clicking emails or completing online forms. This information may include:
Email Address
Name
Address
Company
Location Data
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our viewers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). We use analytics to gather usage information about our website and communications. This helps us understand their effectiveness.
Data you provide with consent is held until you withdraw that consent. Data about how you engage with us, such as reading emails and browsing web pages may be held for up to ten years or more from the last time you engage with us.
How Your Personal Information Is Used
Providing and personalizing our services and website
Responding to your inquiries and requests
Administering orders and accounts
Providing you with information about news and events
Understanding what is of interest to you to improve and provide the most relevant content
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
Sharing
We do not sell or distribute your information to others for the purpose of your being marketed to. We DO NOT share your identifying information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your personal information here. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here.
We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info .
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
Legal Basis
We use consent and legitimate interest as the GDPR basis to store and process your data. The lawful bases are (a) the performance of a contract with you and (b) it is necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products and services, to develop them and grow our business). Legitimate interests include:
Responding to inquiries you make whether by phone, email, contact form, or other method.
Tailoring information based on your activity, such as what content you show interest in.
Delivering electronic information you have requested, such as our e-newsletter.
Consent
By using our site and/or subscribing to our email list, you consent to this Privacy Policy. If at any point you would like to opt-out or withdraw previously given consent please contact us using the details at this end of this policy. All our marketing emails contain unsubscribe links.
Disclosures
We will not sell, barter or rent your data. We may use third party suppliers to help us process your data but only for the purposes identified in this policy.
Our website and communications may include links to third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any third party to whom we link.
Your Rights
Your rights include:
Request the personal data we hold about you.
Complain to a supervisory authority if you believe we have misused your data
Withdraw consent at any time
International information transfers
We use trusted companies to process data outside in the United States. We keep shared data to the minimum necessary, review the privacy policies of those companies and only work with companies we trust to keep your data safe.
Changes
We review and update our privacy policy from time to time. We may notify you of updates by email. It was last updated May 2018.
Contact Information
If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices or would like to withdraw consent, please contact
Poster Pop P16787 Beach Blvd #510
Huntington Beach, CA 92647
714-842-2792
E-mail: hotrod@posterpop.com
Select sub-category
Select sub-category
There are no products in this category.
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Quick Links
Artists
Aaron MarshallBigToeCandyCoopDerek YanigerDirty DonnyForbesKozikKruseMarco AlmeraPigorsPizzSHAGTara McPhersonVince RayVon FrancoBen Von StrawnOther Artists
Genre
Hula TikiSkulls - Day of the DeadHotrod Motorcycle ScooterCats Dogs Wolves AnimalsTattooRockabilly Music Rock and RollDevil and DevilgirlRetro 50s-60s Modern Futuristic 70sMonsters FinksPinup SexyReligiousSurf Skate SportDrinking Drunk
Men's Shirts
Aaron Marshall T-ShirtsAlmera T-ShirtsBigToe T-ShirtsBen Von Strawn T-ShirtsDerek Yaniger T-ShirtsGustavo T-ShirtsDirty Donny T-ShirtsForbes T-ShirtsKozik T-ShirtsKruse T-ShirtsMcPherson T-ShirtsPigors T-ShirtsPizz T-ShirtsVon Franco T-ShirtsVince Ray T-ShirtsClearance T-ShirtsNewest T-Shirts
Blog
Women's
Aaron Marshall BabydollsAlmera BabydollsBen Von Strawn Baby DollsBig Toe BabydollsDerek Yaniger Baby DollsDirty Donny BabydollsForbes BabydollsGustavo BabydollsKozik BabydollsKruse BabydollsPigors BabydollsPizz BabydollsTara McPherson BabydollsVince Ray BabydollsWomen's Baby Doll Tees and Tank TopsNewest Women's ApparelWoman's Sale and Clearance
Stickers
Almera StickersAlmera ReligiousAaron Marshall StickersBigToe StickersCoop StickersDerek Yaniger StickersDirty Donny StickersForbes StickersKozik StickersKruse StickersPigors StickersPizz StickersShag StickersTara McPherson StickersTyson McAdoo StickersVon Franco StickersVince Ray Sticker
Patches
Almera PatchesDirty Donny PatchesCoop PatchesForbes PatchesKozik PatchesKruse PatchesPigors PatchesPizz PatchesScrojo PatchesTara McPherson PatchesVon Franco PatchesVince Ray PatchesDan Collins, Reed, Von Spoon PatchesFD PatchesPLP Patches
Fridge Magnets
Other Merchandise
Tattoo FlashArtists BooksHats and BeaniesMisc MerchClearance
Art and Editions
Fine Art FAQOriginal ArtLimited Edition PrintsArtist's Silkscreen PostersArtist Hand Signed Prints
Custom Printing
Custom Giclee Printing and Art Capture PhotographyCustom Sticker Printing
Warehouse Finds!
Clearance Sale!
Marco AlmeraVince RayBigToeSHAGDirty DonnyKozikCoopPizzGustavo RimadaPigors
